so today we will discuss
how much is the health insurance in
america by family size
not surprisingly the more people in your
family are covered by your health
insurance plan
the more you are likely to pay in
premiums
the average cost for a 40 year old
couple is 954 dollars per month
or
double the cost for an individual
in that age range but adding kids is not
quite as linear
a 40 year old couple with one child
under age 14
would pay an average of 1200 and thirty
dollars per month
and a family of five would pay around
seventeen hundred and eighty two dollars
[Music]
average health insurance premiums by
family size
so here we have a list
of a family type and average monthly
cost if you are an individual of 40 year
old
so your average monthly cost is
477 dollars
[Music]
it seems logical that families would
stick together on health insurance
it's convenient and easy to do so
and together you are more likely to meet
out of the pocket maximum
after which you should not have to pay
out of pocket costs for covered services
but some families might be better off on
separate plans
[Music]
so what is the average health insurance
premiums by age
[Music]
you